Put the green halves in the trash. Go
on, do it. No, you are wasting half if
you do that. It's fine. It's the bad
half.
Yes. All we need are the orange halves.
You stupid [__] The two colors of a
gummy worm are complimentary fruit
flavors. They are supposed to be eaten
together.
Look up. Look up. Look up.
>> No running in the house.
>> What are you doing with the mail?
>> Give that back. It's mine. Please. As if
any pony would be riding to our [__] of
a son of all ponies. No pony loves you.
>> Nothing but junk. Male from one homo to
another.
>> No.
Ah.
Why did you do that?
>> No. Why are you still getting blowies
from that parcel pony instead of working
on the farm?
>> What's it to you? I'm an adult dad. I
can do what I want with my life and get
blowies from whoever I want. And me and
Care Package are legally married now. So
you can't stop us from seeing each
other.
>> Where are you going?
>> I'm getting my medication because it's 7
in the morning. You're making hot
chocolate. I'm letting the pills melt in
the hot chocolate because I have a tight
little throat and they get stuck
otherwise.
You legally can't stop me from taking
them. Take that ridiculously phallic
thing off your head.
>> Give me back my horn. I am in control of
my own life.
>> It's an ice cream cone.
>> Chat GPT says I can put whatever on my
head to make me feel good.
>> You are a worthless earth pony who needs
to learn his place. Stop playing make
believe and wake up to reality.
Well, maybe I have more fun playing
Makebelie than living in this stupid
reality because you two make it hell for
me.
Rule playing as our suppressors the
unicorns is fun to you.
>> Last I checked, unicorns don't got to
pick apples for a living or Pegasus.
Care package says I'm just wasting my
time here.
care package has become a bad influence
on you, telling you you can be free to
do what you want and [__] It's prime
apple picking season, so all members of
the apple family are living under one
roof so that there is not one wasted
second of apple picking. And all you
youngans are living under this roof, you
listen to what the elders say until
apple picking season is over. Apple
picking season won't be over for two
whole months.
I hate you. I hate this family. I hate
my life. You don't use that language in
this house. Shut up, Mom. You're just
jealous that I can walk in a 9-in kitten
heel and you can't, [__]
I'm never coming out of my room again.
>> Well, speak of the godamn devil. It's
care package.
>> Care package?
>> Hi, Care Package. Apple Bottom, I've
never seen you dress in something so
arousing before.
>> You know, it's apple picking season. At
this time of year, all us apples get
together to pick apples. And every day,
one lucky one is chosen to wear the
apple costume and just walk around the
farm to boost everyone's morale. And and
and you don't really care, do you?
>> Did you get my letter? I wanted to know
if you wanted to go lay out in the field
by my house and eat hay since we are
horses.
>> Oh, yeah. I mean, I have to ask my mom
and dad if it's okay. I'd be taking the
day off. So, you know, there might not
be anyone else to wear the costume. Mom,
Dad, can I go lay out in the fields by
our house and eat hay with the mailman?
>> Oh, here we [__] go again.
>> It had better not be that twinkle fairy
homo [__]
>> What did we literally just say? Of
course it's Care Package. Who else would
it be? No pony else likes me.
>> Well, then tell him to go away, but
don't make us look racist.
>> Sorry. My mom and dad said no. Um, my
mom was talking about another twinkle
fairy homo [__]
>> It's fine, Apple Bottom. You don't have
to lie to me. Male ponies face a lot of
racial discrimination. Well, that's it
then. I'll see you tomorrow.
Braburn, I peed in some plastic cups I
got from the Dollar General across the
street. Make sure you and your family
gulps down a whole lot of my Pegasus
piss since Ponyville is being hit by a
massive heatwave. The pterodactyls over
Ponyville are known to target the
dehydrated.
Thank you, Saurin. It's good your balls
always have so much pee in them. Hey,
Apple Bloom, watch this.
I don't understand why I have to be
strung up like this.
>> Just like how some pony has to wear the
apple costume, some pony else has to
play the part of the scarecrow to keep
the pterodactyls above Ponyville at bay.
>> I feel like a piñata.
But at least the view up here isn't so
bad.
>> Some pony switch off with me. I hate
doing this.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday
to you.
my dear friend. Happy birthday
Oh yeah.
La.
Oh, I like it. Happy birthday. See you
all to my own celebrate.
>> You remembered today was my birthday.
Not even my mom and dad remembered.
>> Well, I'm not your mom and dad. Grab
your backpack and let's go.
>> They also say you're a bad influence on
me.
>> What nonsense? If either one of us is a
bad influence on the other, it would be
you.
>> And you seem to like that. Otherwise,
you wouldn't be trying so hard to see
me.
>> If I didn't force my way in, I'd never
get to see you during apple picking
season is all.
>> So, you do want to see me.
>> You thought that it would be okay
at first. The situation could be saved,
of course. But they'd already picked out
your grave and hers. Beware the wrath of
mass crusaders.
Did you lost too close to the sun? Did
they catch you having far too much fun?
Calling me when they say they'll run
something wicked this way. You think I
like my friends.
My life goes
in and sc
my whiskey sour and poison.
Welcome to my underworld where it gets
quite dark. At least you know exactly
who your friends are.
They're the ones with your scar.
You think I like my friends.
My life goes
in and sc
my whiskey sour in poison
to my underworld where it gets quite
far. At least you know exactly who your
friends are.
They stood for me before my ex.
They believed I was in a so
if you can't be good then just be better
at it.
Everyone's got bodies in the attic or
took somebody's land. We'll take you by
the hand and soon you'll learn the art
of never getting caught.
It's a good thing I like my friends
cancel.
I like them cloaked in Gucci and in
scandal break my whiskey sour and
poison.
Yeah, it's a good thing I like my
friends.
So let you have your Apple Bottom. What
did you do? I didn't do anything. It was
like this when I got here. Why do you
always got to blame everything on me?
Some pony help me.
Twilight, what are you doing here?
>> Applejack, the toilet at my house is
clogged, so I came to go pee and poopy
in your outhouse.
>> Well, come inside. The fire is going to
lure the pterodactyls.
>> You don't know who we are.
We're the magic.
We got to play what you wanted to last
night. So this morning you're going to
play my game.
>> Golly G. What kind of game is it?
>> No.
Your son said I'm not here.
I don't know what you're saying.
>> He wants to talk. Apple bottom.
>> How can we talk when you're mute?
>> Apple bottom.
>> I'm asking a question. Am I not allowed
to do that cuz I'm black?
I can't read.
Dad, he doesn't understand.
Nothing at all.
>> Authorities are investigating a series
of violent incidents that occurred late
last night, including multiple stabbings
reported across the downtown area. In a
separate, but possibly related event,
the Apple family's farm was deliberately
set on fire, causing extensive property
damage and the unfortunate demise of
Princess Celestia's own student,
Twilight Sparkle. After the whole
alicorn of death [__] I would think
you'd have told your dad about your
hobbies.
>> Everyone in Ponyville just assumes I was
acting out of line because of the
alicorn magic. My dad doesn't need to
know what I got to do to get off. Can
you imagine what he would think if he
ever found out how he died?
>> I don't know. Your dad is way nicer than
mine, and my dad still hasn't thrown me
out.
>> Why is Pinkie Pie standing in the road
like that?
>> Ah, [__] James. I think the brakes are
stuck again. I'm going under to try and
fix it. So, tell me if I'm about to hit
somebody.
>> What's that? James, are you trying to
tell me a joke?
I love you, James. You're really funny,
even though you are a [__] who is
incapable of speaking.
Hell yeah. I did that. I just did that.
None of you know why what I just did
matters, but I did that.
Cheese and crackers. Where is that
bastard son of ours? I even took the
trouble of inviting all of Apple
Bottom's friends here for his surprise
birthday party.
>> Who's Apple Bottom?
>> If he doesn't show, we're going to have
to cut into the cake ourselves. And I
don't need my fat [__] of a wife who is
also my twin sister getting even fatter.
You hear that, [__] [__] what are
you looking at? Fat [__]
>> Oh, big bro. I screwed up big time. How,
sis? Talk fat [__]
>> I thought today was Apple Bottom's
birthday, but it was yesterday when we
yelled at him.
>> What? No. No, that can't be. I mean, I
never bothered to actually look at his
birth certificate, even on the day you
pushed him out of your because I was so
disgusted by our son being a bottom
[__] So, I just thought you would had
it memorized. I thought you did. I
thought you drew the apple on the
calendar because it's his birthday.
>> No, I draw those apples on the calendar
to remember what days I'm going to beat
him with my belt as punishment for being
ugly. I was going to beat him tonight
before bed.
>> Be careful getting off the scooter.
There's [__] all over the house because
there's only one outhouse on the whole
farm. So, when it's in use, everyone
just shits everywhere. Simon, are we are
we bad parents because we're brother and
sister just like mom and dad said would
happen?
>> I don't know. Maybe. I never thought I
was. Most couples in the Apple family
are brother and sister and beat their
kids. So, I never thought we were any
different.
>> Of course, Apple Bottom wouldn't come
home. Who would come home to [__] ass
ponies like us? Mom, Dad? Apple.
>> Apple Bottom.
Where did you sleep last night? We
missed you.
>> No, you don't. Neither of you do. I know
you two aren't crying for me.
>> Oh, Mr. Care package. Thanks for looking
after our son.
>> Would you like to suck my balls? I mean,
see the cake that my wife picked up at
Walmart. Not that having a wife means
I'm monogamous or anything. We have an
agreement where I can do things with
other horses.
>> That goes for the both of us, by the
way.
>> Happy birthday,
>> Apple Bottom. Look, they were throwing a
surprise party for you all along, and
they almost spelled your name right.
>> Happy birthday
to you.
>> As the birthday pony, I hereby desire
gifts. What does thou have to bestow
upon my ass? Isn't my presence here
enough?
>> No. You eat my ass out like it's a
Salsbury steak every day. As punishment
for not getting me a gift of monetary
value, you will dress up like an apple
and pole dance for me.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Where's Rarity and Twilight?
>> Twilight was using the outhouse on my
farm at the time of the fire. So, she
died.
>> No [__] So, I'm the leader of the main
six now,
>> I guess. But technically, we're the main
four since Pinkie Pie is also dead.
>> Wait, how did Pinkie Pie die?
Is this too much? The purpose of a
funeral, my aesthetically overzealous
friend, is collective lamentation and
remembrance of those who have recently
passed. Not an occasion to flaunt your
fashion sensibilities, says the one in
the oversized suit, which is not the
fault of my own. As a being with no
money, I found it in the dumpster, and
the Ponyville to Taylor would not let me
inside to get it tailored due to my
ghoulish appearance. You could always
ask me to make you something with my
clown powers. I do not want either of us
overusing our magic after the incident
on New Year's. You put me back together
right after. I was fine. It was not fine
right after. It took 1 hour to rebuild
you and then for more for you to wake
up. I would not like a repeat situation
at a funeral of all places. Hey, maybe
if I fall apart again, you could put me
back together differently. Different?
Because all I know how to do is change
my clothes. I want to be taller, less
like Braburn.
I made you in Braburn's likeness because
it was the only template I knew how to
stabilize. As I myself am only Saurin's
magic after all. I never expected you to
want to be anything beyond that. Well,
I'm just saying that the way I am. Some
days it's hard to tell if I'm more
Brabburn or Saurin or Applebottom.
You are not a collaborative error.
Didn't say error.
Sorry.
The shape you gave me is just limiting.
You cannot resent me for making you in
Braburn's likeness. I did not anticipate
you becoming yourself. You are not
Braburn or applebottom or Saurin or
mistake. You are magic that exceeded my
design. That's not exactly reassuring.
It is the only compliment I am capable
of. If I'm magic that ex exceeded your
design, then I will wonder what if the
reason I'm glitching is because I'm
stuck being connected to you. Perhaps
I'm not the one who is unstable and that
it's actually you.
We should stop talking because you are
afraid afraid that my theory is right
and that you're the one that needs
fixing somewhere because I simply do not
enjoy when we argue.
I cannot believe they're doing an open
casket funeral.
I'm sorry, girls. You know I'm poor as
[__] and nobody was going to front four
whole caskets, so you're just going to
have to share one. Unfortunately,
Twilight, because you were annoying, the
only ones who came to the funeral are
Saurin, the Ollicorn Saurin from an
alternate devastated future, Clown
Saurin, a blanket made of Saurin's
magic, and Brayburn. But while we are
few, know that you are loved. Oh. Um, I
just want to say that we're only here
because we accidentally turned left down
the street and came here when we were
actually trying to go to Apple Bottom's
birthday party. And the only reason
we're not leaving is cuz it would be
awkward now if we left. Can I go up to
the podium and say some words?
>> I mean, nobody else is using it. Just
hurry up cuz I want to go home and watch
Heated Rivalry.
>> Twilight Sparkle once committed arson by
trying to burn down my farm in Appalissa
because she's homophobic.
>> Holy [__]
>> So, the fact that she went on to die in
a farm fire is kind of funny if you
think about it.
>> It's as the CEO of Gay Pop, Jojo Siwa,
once said, "Karma's a [__] She should
have known better.
Yeah.
>> Did either of you two [__] see who set
Applejack's farm on fire, killing my
precious sparkle booty?
>> I mean, I did see one pony carrying
around like gas cans, so I think.
>> Quickly, Star Song, describe their hair
color or fur color, or just any
noticeable facial detail in general.
>> Uh, well, the pony clearly had way too
much plastic surgery done. Lip filler
overfilled. Apple bottom.
Woo!
Hallelujah.
Hey,
hey, hey.
Well, here's the deal. He's in a coma
and I regret to tell your asses that he
will probably never wake up again
because of the brain damage. You can
either like keep him like this or pull
the plug. Pull it.
>> As Apple Bottom's legal husband, you do
get the final say. Care package.
>> How much is his life insurance?
>> Same as all ponies. $12 and a3b bag of
oats. A three lb bag of oats could go a
long way if we split it around to all of
us. I speak for all of us when I say
that is a very tempting offer since we
are all horses. Also, we could probably
buy at least two more bags with the $12.
>> What happens to Apple Bottom if we keep
him alive? Well, his brain is like a big
pile of jell-o now, so he won't be
waking up. He's going to be a vegetable,
and you will have to feed, bathe, and
take care of him forever.
>> Oh, I'm not about to do all that. My job
requires me to be out there delivering
mail from 7:00 in the morning to noon
during the weekdays.
>> Noted. Do we know if he is an organ
donor? Has his parents already picked
out a plot in the cemetery? Apple Bottom
is black and black ponies don't get to
be buried in the Ponyill Cemetery. They
go in the landfill behind the Ponyville
Walmart.
>> I'm just asking because if nobody here
has got plans with taking care of the
dead body, I wouldn't mind taking it off
your hands. There are still uses for
dead bodies that are on the fresher
side.
Oh.
mad.
>> It's a long story.
>> Um, I'm sorry to interrupt, but I would
like to sing something for my cousin on
my guitar.
This one is for you, Apple Bottom.
Hey, Braburn.
You're still not done.
>> Hey, Brayburn, let's put the guitar down
for a second. Okay.
>> Was it bad?
>> Yes.
>> No, no, it's just I'm sure we have lots
of others who want to say goodbye also.
Can I show Apple Bottom how good I've
been getting at juggling? I recently
learned how to do it with my feet.
If it's all right. Does everyone think I
could have some alone time with him? I'm
on every pony. Let's go to the hospital
cafeteria and grab some of those jello
cups and take bets on how many
Fluttershy can shove up her [__]
If it were up to me, I would keep you
here. But I know you wouldn't want to
live like this. They never let you up on
stage at the strip club when you're not
even capable of shaking your ass. I
really wish I knew what is going through
your head right now so you could make
your own decision.
Dy,
>> I don't. So, I'm going to do what you
would want. I'm pulling the plug.
I wore your Apple costume because it
smelled like you. I hope you don't mind
me keeping it to remember you by. I
don't want to forget your smell. Maybe
your parents were right. Maybe I was
always a bad influence on you. You would
still be alive if you just stayed home
last night. You asked me at your
birthday why I didn't get you a gift,
and I told you my presents should have
been enough. But the truth is, I was
waiting until after the party to give
you what I really wanted, and I would do
anything to give it to you here and now.
I was going to let you eat a slice of
your birthday cake out of my ass.
>> Apple Bottom is alive.
>> Yay.
If only Twilight and Pinkie Pie were
here to celebrate with us.
>> Brayburn, how did you do that?
>> Well, I opened a portal to heaven, but
Twilight and Pinkie Pie weren't there,
so I opened a portal to hell instead.
>> Wait, so you can just do that?
>> Of course he can. For you see, Saurin
Brayburn is the olicorn of gay. And
because all gay people go to hell,
Brayburn's unique powers allow him to
open the doorway to hell whenever he
wishes. Should the day ever come that
Brayburn dies, he will be the top ruling
overlord of hell, replacing that of
Charlie's own dad, Lucifer.
>> How did he open a portal to heaven then?
>> Brayburn can just do that. Also, I guess
what matters is that we have all our
friends back and safe with us.
>> Okay, well, we're just going to go then.
Clean sweep. What are you doing here?
>> I'm sorry.
>> It is not entirely your fault.
Absolute
freedom. Time regression.
I felt bad about breaking into your
son's room the other night without
telling you and [__] him really hard
while you were asleep right next door
and then startling you by getting shot
in front of you the next day and making
you pay for my hospital bills because my
own family can't afford it. So I snuck
over to apologize by making you
breakfast.
I had to break your window to get in
because your front door was locked. I
don't want any. I only made enough for
you since I knew Care Package was going
to be out of the house early doing his
mail deliveries. I'm jealous that Care
Package has such a good dad. My own dad
hates me. I can see why Care Package
turned out so good. While I
You're a good dad. That's all I wanted
to say. So you don't have to worry about
wondering whether or not you're a part
of Care Package's life. You already are,
just so you know. I just don't want you
to see me as a bad influence on Care
Package. If that makes sense. I want to
be good for him like you are. I'm only
saying it because I think Care Package
is too embarrassed to say it himself.
That's all.
>> What are you two talking about?
>> Nothing you need to hear.
>> All righty. I brought home Taco Bell.
I heard you calling on the megaphone.
You want to see me all alone.
As legend has it, you are quite the
pyro. You light the match to watch it
blow. And if you never come for me, I
might have drowned in the middle.
I swore my loyalty to me myself and I
right before you lit my sky up.
All that time I sat alone in my tower.
You were just holding your powers. Now I
can see it all. See it all. Day one
night you th me out of my grave. Save my
heart from the fate of the failure.
Keep it 100 on the land to your sky.
Pledge allegiance to your hands, your
team, your vibes. Don't care where the
hell you been. Now your mind's about to
be the sleepless night. You've been
dreaming of
made of Ailia.